[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick of logos by Nick comm and
这是尼克·康姆的《商标中的尼克》
in today's tutorial I'll be
在今天的教程中，我将
demonstrating how you can crop a photo
演示如何裁剪照片
using Inkscape and if you'd like to
使用Inkscape，如果您愿意
learn more about how Inkscape works be
了解有关Inkscape如何工作的更多信息
sure to check out the Inkscape master
一定要去看看Inkscape大师
class which is a collection of over 50
类，它是超过50个元素的集合
videos where I go over every single tool
我看过每一种工具的视频
and feature in Inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的特写，我解释
what it is and demonstrate how it works
它是什么，并演示其工作原理
I'll put a link in the description of
我会在描述中添加一个链接
the video if you want to check that out
这个视频如果你想看看的话
so to get started here I'm going to open
所以开始之前，我要开始
up Inkscape the first thing we want to
Up Inkscape我们想要做的第一件事
do is just make sure that we set up our
所做的只是确保我们设置我们的
documents that we're all working with
我们都在处理的文件
this similar setup I'm gonna come up
我会想出类似的设置
here to where it says view we're gonna
在这里，我们将看到这里的景色
want custom selected and then I'm going
希望选择定制，然后我要走了
to go to zoom going to zoom in at 1 to 1
转到ZOOM将在1比1时放大
and then I want to open up the the edit
然后我想打开编辑
objects colors gradients and Stroke menu
对象、颜色、渐变和笔触菜单
with this button up here or you could
用这里的这个按钮，或者你可以
just press control shift F as a keyboard
只需按下Ctrl Shift F即可作为键盘
shortcut and what I want to do now is
捷径，我现在想做的是
import my photo into Inkscape you can do
将我的照片导入Inkscape您可以执行以下操作
that by going to file import and
通过提交导入文件和
navigating to the file on your hard
导航到硬盘上的文件
drive where the photo is located what I
开车去照片所在的地方
like to do is I like to just grab a
我喜欢做的就是抓起一个
folder like this and just click and drag
像这样的文件夹，只需点击并拖动
it into Inkscape like that and I'm just
像这样进入Inkscape，我只是
gonna choose M bed if it asks you if you
如果它问你，我会选择M Bed
want to embed it or link it I just like
我想嵌入或链接它，我只是喜欢
to go with embed and there we go there's
去嵌入，然后我们就去那里
the photo I'm gonna be cropping let me
我要剪裁的照片让我
zoom out a little bit I'm gonna hold
稍微缩小一点，我会按住
ctrl and roll down the mouse wheel to
按住Ctrl键并向下滚动鼠标滚轮以
zoom out a little bit what I'm gonna be
把我要做的事情放大一点
doing here is removing the subject from
这里所做的是将主题从
the background here now before we get
在我们得到之前，这里的背景
started I just have to mention that this
一开始我不得不提一下这件事
is the sort of thing that would be
是一种会成为
better suited for an application like
更适合像这样的应用
inkscape isn't really designed for
Inkscape实际上并不是为
working with photos like this it's more
与这样的照片合作，它更多
for vector design but if you don't feel
向量设计，但如果你不觉得
like downloading if you're not a
比如下载，如果你不是
user and you don't feel like downloading
用户，而您不想下载
and installing and learning how to
以及安装和学习如何
use a new piece of software this can
使用一个新的软件，这可以
absolutely be done with Inkscape in fact
事实上，完全可以用Inkscape完成
i do this with Inkscape all the time so
我一直都在用Inkscape这样做，所以
just wanted to throw that out there
我只是想把它扔出去
before we get started so let me get
在我们开始之前，让我先
started here I'm gonna zoom in a little
从这里开始，我要放大一点
bit to zoom in and out again who's
一次又一次放大和缩小谁是
holding ctrl and rolling up and down the
按住Ctrl键并上下滚动
mouse wheel we'll be doing that a lot
鼠标滚轮我们会经常这么做的
throughout this tutorial we'll also be
在本教程中，我们还将
moving the page around like this to do
像这样移动页面以执行以下操作
this I'm pressing down the mouse wheel
我正在按下鼠标滚轮
and moving the mouse just basic
移动鼠标只是最基本的
navigation tools you're gonna have to
导航工具，你将不得不
keep in mind while working on this I'm
在做这件事时请记住，我是
gonna start over here about the lower
从这里开始，大约从下面开始
right edge of the subject I'm going to
主题的右边，我要谈到
grab the bezel
抓住挡板
which is over here or you could present
哪一个在这里，或者你可以展示
beyond the keyboard and I'm going to
在键盘之外，我要
click to create a point outside of the
单击以在外部创建点
photo here and I'm going to start
在这里拍照，我要开始
creating points going around the edge of
创建环绕边缘的点
the subject here just like this and if
这里的主题就是这样，如果
you notice these lines aren't exactly
你注意到这些台词并不完全是
smooth they're not following the
很顺利，他们没有跟上
contours of the subjects outline here
主题的轮廓在这里勾勒出来
but that's okay we're gonna go back and
但没关系，我们要回去
fix that later so don't worry about that
以后再解决，所以不用担心这个问题
right now just go ahead and click to
现在，只需继续并点击
create these points going around the
创建这些围绕
subject and this is a pretty big photo
主题，这是一张很大的照片
with a lot of points to create so what
有很多积分要创造，那又如何？
I'm gonna do is I'm gonna do this and
我要做的就是我要这么做
I'm gonna fast forward and I'll catch up
我要快进了，我会赶上的
with you what I'm done
和你在一起我做了什么
okay so as you can see here I went
好的，正如你所看到的，我去了
around the outside of the subject here
围绕着这个主题的外部
and I've traced an outline coming out to
我已经勾勒出了一个轮廓
the other end of the photo what I'm
照片的另一端是我
gonna do is I'm just gonna bring this
我要做的就是把这个
line around outside the photo over here
在照片外面排起长队在这里
and connect it back to the starting
并将其连接回起点
point by clicking on that and it's gonna
点击它，它就会
create a shape there like that if you
在那里创建一个这样的形状，如果您
notice now we have a shape going around
请注意，现在我们有了一个围绕周围的形状
the outline of the subject let me go
这个题目的提纲使我印象深刻。
ahead and undo that what we want to do
然后撤销我们想要做的事
now is we want to account for these
现在我们要解释的是这些
negative space areas within this within
这里面的负空间区域
the subject here assuming your photo
这里的主题假设你的照片
does have these negative space areas if
有这些负空间区域，如果
it doesn't don't worry about it but
它并不担心，但是
we're gonna have to eliminate these
我们将不得不消除这些
areas like between the hand and the
手掌和手掌之间的区域
shoulder over here and the same over
肩膀这边和那边一样
here on this side so I'm gonna do is I'm
在这一边，所以我要做的是我
gonna create more shapes inside of here
将在这里创造更多的形状
doing the same thing just creating
做同样的事情，只是创造了
following along the contours of the
沿着轮廓线走下去
subject with the Bezier pen by creating
用贝塞尔钢笔创作主题
points like that I'll put one right
像这样的观点，我会纠正其中一个
there another one here for the hair
这里还有一根头发的
okay so once you're done accounting for
好的，所以一旦你算完了
all of the areas of negative space what
负空间的所有区域是什么
we want to do is combine them all
我们想要做的就是把它们结合起来
together by grabbing the select tool
一起通过抓取选择工具
over here I'm gonna grab this area right
在这里，我要抓住这个区域的权利
here I'm gonna hold shift and click on
在这里，我将按住Shift键并单击
the other one so that we can select
另一个，这样我们就可以选择
multiples at a time I'm gonna hold shift
一次多次我要按住Shift键
click on that one and then hold shift
单击该按钮，然后按住Shift键
and click on that one and you should
点击那个按钮，你应该
have all of them selected if you
如果您选择了所有选项，请选择
shift-click them and what I want to do
按住Shift键并单击它们以及我要执行的操作
is unify them together by going to path
就是通过去PATH把它们统一起来
Union and now what I want to do is take
联合，现在我想要做的是
that group of unified objects and
这组统一的对象和
subtract them from the main outline that
从主要提纲中减去它们
we created in the background over there
我们在那边的背景里创作的
so with this group of objects selected
所以选择了这组对象后
I'm going to hold shift and I'm going to
我要轮班，我要
click on the original outline and I'm
点击原始大纲，我就会
gonna go to path difference and nothing
我要去路径差，什么都没有
is going to change visually on the
将在视觉上发生变化
screen but if you change the color of
屏幕，但如果您更改
the object here you'll see it now fits
你会看到这里的物体现在适合
the shape of the subject here if you see
主体的形状，如果你看到
I missed that one so let me just
我错过了那个，所以让我
subtract that as well
也减去那个。
path difference there we go okay so what
路径差异在那里，我们走好了，那又如何
I want to do now is I want to go back to
我现在想做的就是我想回去
where what I was talking about earlier
我之前谈到的地方
with those rough lines I want to make
我想用这些粗略的线条
them smooth so let me turn off the fill
它们很光滑，所以让我关掉填充物
color of this and let me zoom in on this
这个的颜色，让我放大这个
area over here where we started out let
我们开始的地方就在这里
me go to the edit pads by nodes tool
转到按结点编辑焊盘工具
over here or a good pressed end on the
在这里，或者一个很好的熨平的结束
keyboard let me just fix that one it's
键盘，让我修一下那个，它是
not quite right there we go what I'm
不是很好，我们要做的就是我
gonna do is I'm gonna click and drag
我要做的就是点击并拖动
over this node right here and I'm gonna
在这里的这个节点上，我要
click on this button that says make
点击这个按钮，上面写着Make
selected nodes Auto smooth and it's
选定节点自动平滑，它的
gonna make that node smooth so that it's
让这个结点变得光滑，这样它就
no longer like a rough like a like a
不再喜欢粗暴喜欢喜欢
polygonal sort of corner it's gonna make
它将形成一个多边形的角落
it smooth I'll do the same thing with
它很光滑，我也会做同样的事情
this node over here make that smooth and
这里的这个节点使它变得平滑和
what we're gonna do is we're gonna go
我们要做的是我们要去
through and do this with all of these
通过所有这些来做这件事
nodes but we're not gonna do this node
节点，但我们不会使用这个节点
by node because that would take forever
按节点，因为这将永远花费时间
what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna select
我要做的是我要选择
these multiples at a time by holding
一次通过持有这些倍数
shift and clicking on them you can't
按住Shift键并单击它们，但您不能
select multiples at a time as I'm doing
像我这样一次选择多个
here just hold your shift and click and
在这里，只需按住Shift键并单击
drag over them and make sure not to
将它们拖过并确保不会
select any corner so let me show you
选择任何角落，让我向您展示
what I mean I'm gonna come over here I'm
我的意思是我要来这里我是
not gonna select that node because it's
不会选择该节点，因为它是
a corner I don't want to make that
一个我不想做的角落
smooth so with these selected let me
顺畅的让我选择了这些
make those Auto smooth and if you notice
使这些自动平滑，如果您注意到
it's now smooth it now follows the
它现在很平滑，它现在遵循
contours of the subject they're a little
主题的轮廓，它们有点
more closely if you take a corner node
如果你取一个角节点，会更接近
and you make that smooth you're gonna
你让这一切变得顺畅你就会
end up with that we don't want to end up
以我们不想结束的方式结束
with that right there so let me undo
就在那里，所以让我解开
that by hitting ctrl Z
通过按Ctrl Z键
and I'm gonna go through and select more
我会仔细检查并选择更多
of these nodes making sure to avoid the
，以确保避免
corners like I previously mentioned let
就像我之前提到的那样
me see let me see how this looks okay
我看看，让我看看这个看起来怎么样？
good
好的
let me go through here and do this as
让我穿过这里，这样做就可以了
well I'm gonna go through the entire
好的，我会从头到尾
image and do this with all of these
图像，并使用所有这些
nodes and then once again I'll I'll
结点，然后再一次我会我会
catch up if you when I'm done
如果我做完了你就跟上我
okay so I finished going through and
好的，我看完了，然后
smoothing out all of the nodes of the
的所有节点进行平滑处理
the outline here now we're ready to crop
这里的轮廓现在我们可以裁剪了
so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna grab
所以我要做的是我要抓住
the select tool I want to take this
选择工具我想拿着这个
object right here I just want to give
反对，我只是想给你
this a different color look I'm gonna
这是一个不同的颜色，我要
make this green for example just so we
例如，让这个绿色，这样我们就可以
can see what exactly will be cropping
可以看到到底要剪些什么
right here now what I want to do is get
现在我想做的就是
rid of that outline so I'm gonna hold
去掉那个轮廓，所以我要拿着
shift I'm gonna click on this little red
Shift我要点击这个小红色
X down here in the bottom left corner
X在这里的左下角
and let me just bring the opacity of
让我来介绍一下不透明的
this down a little bit just so I can see
把这个放低一点，这样我就能看到了
I just want to double check and make
我只想再检查一遍，然后确定
sure that everything that I'm cropping
确保我种植的所有东西
out here looks good and everything it
这里看起来很好，一切都很好
does it looks like everything looks good
一切看起来都很好吗？
here looks like it's gonna be a clean
看起来这将是一个干净的
crop so what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
裁剪，所以我要做的是
hold shift and I'm gonna click on the
按住Shift键，我将单击
object right there both the object in
对象就在那里，其中的对象
the photo we want them both selected and
我们希望他们都被选中的照片
then we'll go to object clip set and if
然后我们将转到对象剪辑集，如果
you notice they're the background of the
你会注意到他们是
of the photo is now gone in fact you can
这张照片现在不见了，事实上你可以
create a rectangle let me go to the
创建一个矩形，让我转到
rectangle tool right here
矩形工具就在这里
create a rectangle grab the Select tool
创建一个矩形抓取选择工具
send this to the bottom and you can see
把这个送到底部，你就会看到
we have our subject cropped out from the
我们把我们的主题从
background now if any point you want to
背景资料，如果你想知道的话
go back and remove this crop you just go
回去把这些庄稼移走你就走吧
to object clip objects clip release and
对象剪裁对象剪裁释放和
it'll release it so you can go back to
它会释放它，这样你就可以回到
the original photo of how it was
它是如何的原始照片
otherwise you can just leave it right
否则你可以把它放在右边
there as it is and that is how you can
它就在那里，这就是你可以
go about cropping a photo with Inkscape
使用Inkscape裁剪照片
if you have any questions let me know
如果你有任何问题，请告诉我
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
[Music]
[音乐]